<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="version_template">v%s</string>
    <string name="edit_gesture_hint">اضغط على التطبيق المصغر بإصبعين للتحريك وضبط الحجم.</string>
    <string name="edit_gesture_hint_2">حسناً! اضغط بإصبعين لإخفاء عناصر الواجهة.</string>
    <string name="hide_gesture_hint">اضغط على اطار التطبيق المصغر بثلاث اصابع لإخفائة مؤقتاً. سيبقى مخفياً حتى تطفئ وتشغل الشاشة مجددا.</string>
    <string name="hide_gesture_hint_2">اطفئ واعد تشغيل الشاشة مجددا لجلب التطبيق المصغر.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_desc">التطبيقات المصغرة لشاشة القفل تحتاح الى خدمة إمكانية الوصول للعرض على شاشة القفل ومركز الاشعارات. لن يتم جمع بيانات. ولا إجراء سيتم في الجهاز.</string>
    <string name="add_widget">اضافة تطبيق مصغر</string>
    <string name="grant">سماح</string>
    <string name="settings">الاعدادات</string>
    <string name="yes">نعم</string>
    <string name="no">لا</string>
    <string name="add">اضافة</string>
    <string name="add_id">اضافة معرف</string>
    <string name="usage">الاستخدام</string>
    <string name="back_up">نسخ احتياطي</string>
    <string name="restore">استعادة</string>
    <string name="id_list">قائمة المعرفات</string>
    <string name="more_info">مزيد من المعلومات</string>
    <string name="search">بحث</string>
    <string name="preview">معاينة</string>
    <string name="close_app">إغلاق التطبيق</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">سياسة الخصوصية</string>
    <string name="shortcut">اختصار</string>
    <string name="enabled">مفعل</string>
    <string name="disabled">معطل</string>
    <string name="accessibility_settings">خدمة إمكانية الوصول</string>
    <string name="battery_whitelist">قائمة السماح للبطارية</string>
    <string name="back">رجوع</string>
    <string name="clear">مسح</string>
    <string name="drawer_enabled">الدرج مفعل</string>
    <string name="frame_enabled">الاطار مفعل</string>
    <string name="add_id_hint">com.android.systemui:id/some_id_here</string>
    <string name="category_appearance">المظهر</string>
    <string name="category_behavior">السلوك</string>
    <string name="category_visibility">الظور</string>
    <string name="category_layout">التخطيط</string>
    <string name="category_interaction">التفاعل</string>
    <string name="category_debug">تصحيح الاخطاء</string>
    <string name="remove">ازالة</string>
    <string name="expand_down">تمديد للأسفل</string>
    <string name="expand_up">تمديد للأعلى</string>
    <string name="expand_left">تمديد لليسار</string>
    <string name="expand_right">تمديد لليمين</string>
    <string name="reconfigure">اعادة ضبط</string>
    <string name="center_vertically">وسط عامودياً</string>
    <string name="center_horizontally">وسط افقياً</string>
    <string name="move">تحريك</string>
    <string name="hide">إخفاء</string>
    <string name="shortcut_icon">إختصار الايقونة</string>
    <string name="expand">تمديد</string>
    <string name="alert_remove_widget_confirm">Remove Widget?</string>
    <string name="alert_remove_widget_confirm_desc">Are you sure you want to remove this widget?</string>
    <string name="main_screen_social_mastodon">Mastodon</string>
    <string name="main_screen_social_mastodon_desc">Follow me on Mastodon for updates about my apps and random development-related nonsense.</string>
    <string name="main_screen_social_website">Website</string>
    <string name="main_screen_social_website_desc">Check out my website if you\'re that bored.</string>
    <string name="main_screen_social_email">Email</string>
    <string name="main_screen_social_email_desc">Send me an email if you have a question or problem. Please include as much detail as possible. Just telling me \"it doesn\'t work\" just wastes everyone\'s time.</string>
    <string name="main_screen_social_telegram">Telegram</string>
    <string name="main_screen_social_telegram_desc">If email isn\'t your thing, you can ask your question in my Telegram server. Please mention which app you\'re using, as this server is for all of the ones I\'ve developed.</string>
    <string name="main_screen_social_github">GitHub</string>
    <string name="main_screen_social_github_desc">Lockscreen Widgets is open source! If you\'re a developer or tinkerer interested in helping to improve the project (or you just want to check out the source), tap here.</string>
    <string name="main_screen_social_patreon">Patreon</string>
    <string name="main_screen_social_patreon_desc">For $1 every month, you get access to all of my paid apps, along with some exclusive stuff.</string>
    <string name="main_screen_accessibility_not_started">The Accessibility Service isn\'t currently running. This may be because you need to allowlist Lockscreen Widgets from your phone\'s battery optimizations, or you may just need to toggle it off and on again in Settings.</string>
    <string name="intro_privacy_policy_desc">Lockscreen Widgets doesn\'t collect any data beyond what\'s needed for crash analysis. Learn more below.</string>
    <string name="main_screen_privacy_policy_desc">Lockscreen Widgets doesn\'t collect any data beyond what\'s needed for crash analysis. Tap here to learn more.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_hide_when_notifications_shown">Hide when Showing Notifications</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_hide_when_notifications_shown_desc">Hide the widget frame while there are notifications being shown. This requires the use of a Notification Listener Service. You don\'t have to grant this permission right now.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_page_indicator_behavior">Page Indicator Behavior</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_page_indicator_behavior_hidden">Always Hidden</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_page_indicator_behavior_auto_hide">Auto-Hide</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_page_indicator_behavior_shown">Always Shown</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_hide_on_notification_shade">Hide when Notification Shade Shown</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_hide_on_notification_shade_desc">Try to hide the widget frame when the notification shade is pulled down. This may not work on all devices.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_hide_on_security_input">Hide on Security Input</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_hide_on_security_input_desc">Try to hide the widget frame when the PIN/pattern/password input view is shown. This may not work on all devices.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_animate_show_hide">Animate Show/Hide</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_animate_show_hide_desc">Animate the showing/hiding of the widget frame.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_debug_log">Debug Logs</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_debug_log_desc">Turn this on to create verbose logs of Lockscreen Widgets\' state.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_clear_debug_log">Clear Debug Logs</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_clear_debug_log_desc">Clear previous debug logs.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_export_debug_log">Export Debug Logs</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_export_debug_log_desc">Export debug logs to a file.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_frame_col_count">Columns per Page</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_frame_row_count">Rows per Page</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_show_debug_id_view">Show Debug ID View</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_show_debug_id_view_desc">Overlay the widget frame with a list of View IDs it detects on the current screen. Useful for debugging and finding IDs that can be used to detect various lock screen states.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_accessibility_event_delay">Accessibility Event Delay</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_accessibility_event_delay_desc">Sets the delay between Accessibility Events that Lockscreen Widgets responds to. Shorter values mean the frame will respond faster to changes, at the potential cost of device performance and battery life.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_non_present_ids">Hide on Non-Present IDs</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_non_present_ids_desc">Lockscreen Widgets will hide itself when these IDs are not on-screen. You can find which IDs should go here by enabling both Debug switches and looking at the IDs that are highlighted in red when you want the frame to be hidden.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_present_ids">Hide on Present IDs</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_present_ids_desc">Lockscreen Widgets will hide itself when these IDs are on-screen. You can find which IDs should go here by enabling both Debug switches and looking at the IDs that are highlighted in green when you want the frame to be hidden.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_show_in_notification_center">Show when Notification Shade is Fully Expanded</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_show_in_notification_center_desc">Samsung\'s One UI 1 (Pie) and One UI 2 (10) have some empty space to the right of the clock when the notification center is fully expanded. Enabling this option will cause the widget frame to appear when the shade is fully expanded. This state has its own independent positioning and size.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_show_on_main_lock_screen">Show on Main Lock Screen</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_show_on_main_lock_screen_desc">اذا كنت تستخدم خيار الاظهار في مركز الاشعارات ،قد لا تريد التطبيق يظهر في شاشة القفل الرئيسية. عطل هذا الخيار ليكون الاطار ظاهر حينما يكون مركز الاشعارات ممد بالكامل.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_corner_radius">زاوية نصف القطر</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_corner_radius_desc">تغيير مدى دائرية اطار الزوايا للتطبيق المصغر.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_widget_corner_radius">نصف قطر التطبيق المصغر</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_widget_corner_radius_desc">تغيير مدى دائرية اطار الزوايا للتطبيق المصغر.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_background_color">لون الخلفية</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_background_color_desc">حدد لون الخلفية لإطار التطبيق المصغر،تضمن الشفافية.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_masked_mode">الوضع المقنع (تجريبي)</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_masked_mode_desc">محاولة وضع مقنع لرسم الخلفية كخلفية لإطار القطعة. على جهاز متوافق، هذا سيعطي مظهر إطار شفاف، مع السماح لك بتدوين عناصر واجهة المستخدم.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_masked_mode_dim_amount">مدى تضليل الوضع المقنع</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_masked_mode_dim_amount_desc">بعض الأجهزة تعتم الخلفية على شاشة القفل قليلاً. قم بضبط هذا للمطابقة.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_touch_protection">حماية اللمس</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_touch_protection_desc">تجاهل لمسات على إطار التطبيق المصغر عندما يكون مستشعر القرب مغطا.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_request_unlock">سماح للقفل / تجاهل مركز الاشعارات</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_request_unlock_desc">اذا حدد التطبيق ان التطبيقات المصغرة ستقوم بتشغيل تطبيق،سيسمح بإلغاء القفل وتجاهل مركز الاشعارات. عطل هذا الخيار لتجنب هذا السلوك.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_hide_on_facewidgets">اخفاء في شاشة وجه التطبيق المصغر</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_hide_on_facewidgets_desc">اخف الاطار حينما يكون وجه التطبيق المصغر معروض.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_hide_in_landscape">إخفاء في الوضع الأفقي</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_hide_in_landscape_desc">اخف التطبيق المصغر حينما يكون الجهاز في الوضع الأفقي.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_separate_position_for_lock_nc">افصل مكان مركز الاشعارات حينما يكون مقفل</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_separate_position_for_lock_nc_desc">على واجهة one UI 3، يختلف تخطيط مركز الإشعارات اختلافا طفيفا عند قفله وفتحه. تمكين هذا لإستخدام وضع منفصل لإطار التطبيق المصغر في هاتين الحالتين.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_lock_widget_frame">قفل اطار التطبيق المصغر</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_lock_widget_frame_desc">عند تمكين هذا ، سيتجاهل إطار التطبيق المصغر جميع اللمسات المباشرة. لن تتمكن من نقله أو تعديل التطبيقات المصغرة من الإطار، لكن إيماءة الإخفاء الثلاثية الأصابع ستظل تعمل وستبقى قادراً على التفاعل مع التطبيقات المصغرة.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_ignore_widget_touches">تجاهل لمسات التطبيقات المصغرة</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_ignore_widget_touches_desc">عند التمكين، سيتم تجاهل اللمسات على التطبيقات المصغرة. هذا سيمنع تشغيل التطبيق بشكل عرضي، ولكن أيضا سيمنع التفاعل مع التطبيقات المصغره.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_lock_widget_drawer">قفل درج التطبيقات المصغره</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_lock_widget_drawer_desc">عند تمكين هذا، سيصبح تخطيط درج القطعة مقفلا. لن تتمكن من إزالة أو تغيير حجم أو إعادة ترتيب التطببقات المصغره، ولكن ستبقى قادراً على التفاعل معها.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_animation_duration">مدرة المؤثر الحركي</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_animation_duration_desc">تعيين الوقت الذي تستغرقه عملية تلاشي الرسوم المتحركة/تلاشي الرسوم المتحركة لإكمالها.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_back_up_widgets">نسخ احتياطي</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_back_up_widgets_desc">النسخ الاحتياطي للتطبيقات المصغره الحالية والاختصارات. هذا لا يشمل البلاطات للتطبيقات المصغرة.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_restore_widgets">استعادة</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_restore_widgets_desc">استعادة التطبيقات المصغره والاختصارات من النسخة الاحتياطية. هذا سيحل محل الأدوات والاختصارات الموجودة. هذا لا يشمل البلاطات للتطبيقات المصغرة.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_blur_background">خلفية ضبابية</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_blur_background_desc">على أجهزة سامسونج وأندرويد 12 وما بعدها، من الممكن طمس خلفية الإطار. هذا لن ينطبق حيث ينطبق الوضع المقنع، وقد لا يعمل على جميع الأجهزة أو في وضع توفير البطارية.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_blur_drawer_background_desc">على أجهزة سامسونج وأندرويد 12 وما بعدها، من الممكن طمس خلفية الدرج. قد لا يعمل هذا على جميع الأجهزة أو في وضع توفير البطارية.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_blur_background_amount">كمية الضبابية</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_blur_background_amount_desc">تعيين كم يجب أن تكون الخلفية ضبابية.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_remember_position">تذكر الموقع</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_remember_position_desc">بشكل افتراضي، تتذكر التطبيقات المصغره الصفحة التي كانت في آخر مرة كانت على الشاشة وتمرير إلى ذلك الموقع في كل مرة تظهر فيها. عطل هذا الخيار لجعل تطبيقات قفل الشاشة تعرض دائماً الصفحة الأولى عند ظهورها.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_hide_on_edge_panels">اخفاء على قائمة الحافه</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_hide_on_edge_panels_desc">إخفاء إطار التطبيقات المصغره عندما تكون لوحة حافة سامسونج مفتوحة.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_hide_on_present_apps">إخفاء التطبيقات الحالية</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_hide_on_present_apps_desc">اختر التطبيقات التي يجب أن تجعل إطار التطبيقات المصغره يختفي إذا كانت تظهر على شاشة القفل.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_separate_layout">تخطيط العرض منفصل للعرض الأفقي</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_separate_layout_desc">تعيين مواقع وأحجام مختلفة لإطار التطبيق المصغر في الوضع الأفقي.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_force_widget_update">فرض تحديث التطبيق المصغر</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_force_widget_update_desc">عندما تظهر التطبيقات المصغره على الشاشة، لا يتم دائما إرسال تحديثات التطبيقات المصغره المعلقة. للعمل حول هذا، التطبيقات المصغره قفل الشاشة تجبر جميع التطبيقات المصغره على إعادة التحميل بشكل افتراضي، الأمر الذي يمكن أن يسبب وميض قصير. قم بتعطيل هذا الخيار لتجنب الوميض، على حساب التطبيقات المصغرة المحدثة.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_hide_when_keyboard_shown">إخفاء عند عرض لوحة المفاتيح</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_hide_when_keyboard_shown_desc">إخفاء إطار التطبيق المصغر عندما تكون لوحة مفاتيح مرئية حاليا على الشاشة.</string>
    <string name="intro_welcome_title">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="intro_welcome_desc">Lockscreen Widgets is a simple app with a simple purpose: to bring back Android KitKat\'s lock screen widgets. Your widgets will show up in a simple paged slider on the lockscreen.</string>
    <string name="intro_usage_title">Basic Usage</string>
    <string name="intro_usage_desc">Tap the \"plus\" page to add a widget, press and hold to reorder/resize/remove widgets in the list, and tap anywhere on the frame with two fingers to move/resize the frame or add a widget. You can also tap with three fingers to hide the widget frame until the screen is turned off and on again.</string>
    <string name="intro_accessibility_title">Accessibility</string>
    <string name="intro_accessibility_desc">To be able to display on the lock screen, you\'ll need to activate Lockscreen Widgets\' Accessibility Service. This app doesn\'t collect any data from your screen.</string>
    <string name="intro_notification_listener_title">Notification Listener</string>
    <string name="intro_notification_listener_desc">Lockscreen Widgets can hide the widget frame while there are notifications displayed. To do so, you\'ll need to enable the Notification Listener. You don\'t have to grant this right now.</string>
    <string name="intro_read_storage_title">Read External Storage</string>
    <string name="intro_read_storage_desc">Lockscreen Widgets has a \"masking\" mode, where it will use your wallpaper as the widget frame background, causing it to seem transparent, while also being able to cover lock screen elements. To do this, Lockscreen Widgets needs permission to be able to read your device\'s storage. You don\'t have to grant this right now. If you\'re running Lollipop, this permission is already granted. More details are available in the privacy policy.</string>
    <string name="intro_read_external_storage_desc_13_addendum">On Android 13 and later, you will need to grant READ_MEDIA_IMAGES and use App Ops paired with Shizuku to grant this READ_EXTERNAL_STORAGE.</string>
    <string name="intro_battery_optimization">Battery Optimization</string>
    <string name="intro_battery_optimization_desc">Many devices, including those running MIUI and EMUI, have incredibly aggressive battery management. This can cause Lockscreen Widgets to be killed when you don\'t want it to be. Click the button below to read how you can allowlist Lockscreen Widgets on your particular device.</string>
    <string name="intro_done_title">All Done!</string>
    <string name="intro_done_desc">That\'s it! Check your lock screen and you should now see the widget frame!</string>
    <string name="usage_add_widget">Add Widget</string>
    <string name="usage_add_widget_desc">Adding a widget can be done in one of three ways. If the widget pager doesn\'t have any widgets added, simply press the \"plus\" button that appears inside it. Otherwise, you can tap the frame with two fingers and then tap the \"plus\" button on the top right of the frame. You can also add a widget from the app itself, by tapping the \"plus\" button at the top right of the main screen.</string>
    <string name="usage_modify_frame">Modify Frame</string>
    <string name="usage_modify_frame_desc">If the frame is in the way, or you want it to be a different size, you can easily move and resize it. Simply tap the frame itself with two fingers to show the editing interface.</string>
    <string name="usage_temp_hide">Temp Hide</string>
    <string name="usage_temp_hide_desc">If you need to just hide the widget frame for a while, tap it with three fingers. You can also enter the editing interface with a two-finger tap and press the eye button in the top left. This will hide the frame until the screen is turned off and on again.</string>
    <string name="usage_reorder_widgets">Reorder Widgets</string>
    <string name="usage_reorder_widgets_desc">To change the order of the widgets, simply long-press the widget you want to move and drag it to where you want it to be.</string>
    <string name="usage_remove_widgets">Remove/Resize Widgets</string>
    <string name="usage_remove_widgets_desc">To remove a widget, long-press it without dragging and tap the red button that appears in the top right. Long-pressing a widget will also show four \"draggers\" around the edges, which you can use to resize the widget.</string>
    <string name="usage_id_blacklists">ID Blacklists</string>
    <string name="usage_id_blacklists_desc">All phones are different, and it\'s possible that the built-in hiding options don\'t work on your device. Or maybe you want to implement a hiding behavior of your own. This can be implemented with the \"Hide on Present IDs\" and \"Hide on Non-Present IDs\" options. Any IDs you add to the former will cause the widget frame to hide when Lockscreen Widgets detects any of those IDs on-screen. Any IDs you add to the latter will cause the widget frame to hide when Lockscreen Widgets does <i>not</i> detect any of those IDs on-screen. You can find out which IDs should be added by enabling both Debug options and seeing which IDs are highlighted in green or red.</string>
    <string name="usage_widget_tiles">One UI Widget Tiles</string>
    <string name="usage_widget_tiles_desc">On Samsung One UI devices, you can run a limited subset of widgets using your QS tiles. Add the Lockscreen Widgets tiles to your quick settings, and tap the text of the tile to get started. Widgets that involve dynamic lists, like email or calendar widgets, likely won\'t work. This isn\'t something that can be fixed.</string>
    <string name="tile_show_in_notification_center">Show in NC</string>
    <string name="configure_widget_error">Unable to configure the widget %s due to lack of permissions. Please contact the app developer or device manufacturer.</string>
    <string name="bind_widget_error">Unable to bind the widget %s due to lack of permissions. Please contact the app developer or device manufacturer.</string>
    <string name="invalid_id_backup_error">Invalid ID list.</string>
    <string name="enable_debug_log_msg">Please enable the debug log option to see IDs here.</string>
    <string name="touch_protection_active">Touch protection active. Please uncover the proximity sensor.</string>
    <string name="launch_shortcut_error">Unable to launch shortcut.</string>
    <string name="create_shortcut_error">Unable to create shortcut.\n%s</string>
    <string name="accessibility_not_started">The Accessibility Service hasn\'t started yet. Please wait.</string>
    <string name="unable_to_restore_widgets">Unable to restore widgets.</string>
    <string name="unable_to_back_up_widgets">Unable to back up widgets.</string>
    <string name="unable_to_launch">Unable to launch.</string>
    <string name="open_close_toolbar">Open/Close Toolbar</string>
    <string name="open_widget_drawer">Open Widget Drawer</string>
    <string name="open_drawer">Open Drawer</string>
    <string name="close_widget_drawer">Close Drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer">Drawer</string>
    <string name="handle">Handle</string>
    <string name="error">Error</string>
    <string name="close_on_empty_tap">Tap Empty Space to Close Drawer</string>
    <string name="close_on_empty_tap_desc">With this enabled, tapping outside of the area of any widgets will cause the drawer to close.</string>
    <string name="show_drawer_handle">إظهار شريط الدرج</string>
    <string name="show_drawer_handle_desc">إضافة شريك إلى جانب الشاشة التي يمكن سحبها لفتح الدرج.</string>
    <string name="show_drawer_handle_shadow">إظهار ضل شريط الدرج</string>
    <string name="show_drawer_handle_shadow_desc">إظهار ظل خلف شريط الدرج.</string>
    <string name="drawer_handle_height">ارتفاع شريط الدرج</string>
    <string name="drawer_handle_height_desc">قم بتعيين مدى طول شريط الدرج.</string>
    <string name="drawer_handle_width">ارتفاع شريط الدرج</string>
    <string name="drawer_handle_width_desc">قم بتعيين مدى اتساع شريط الدرج. يمكن أن يكون هذا مفيداً للشاشات مع حواف منحنية.</string>
    <string name="drawer_handle_color">لون شريط الدرج</string>
    <string name="drawer_handle_color_desc">قم بتعيين لون شريط الدرج.</string>
    <string name="drawer_background_color">لون خلفية الدرج</string>
    <string name="drawer_background_color_desc">تعيين لون الخلفية للدرج.</string>
    <string name="drawer_column_count">عدد أعمدة الدرج</string>
    <string name="drawer_column_count_desc">اختر عدد الأعمدة التي يجب أن يكون بها تخطيط الدرج.</string>
    <string name="drawer_side_padding">الحشوة الجانبية للدرج</string>
    <string name="drawer_side_padding_desc">تعيين مقدار المساحة التي يجب أن تظهر بين جانبي الشاشة وحواف التطبيقات المصغره الخارجية.</string>
    <string name="show_only_when_locked">إظهار فقط عند القفل</string>
    <string name="show_only_when_locked_desc">إظهار شريط الدرج فقط عندما يكون الجهاز على شاشة القفل.</string>
    <string name="allow_show_frame">السماح بعرض الإطار</string>
    <string name="disallow_show_frame">عدم السماح بعرض الإطار</string>
    <string name="frame_allowed_to_show">الإطار المسموح به للعرض</string>
    <string name="is_showing_frame">هو عرض الإطار</string>
    <string name="is_showing_drawer">هو عرض الدرج</string>
    <string name="force_show_frame">فرض إظهار الإطار</string>
    <string name="unforce_show_frame">التراجع عن فرض اظهار إلاطار</string>
    <string name="frame_forced_to_show">اجبار عرض الاطار</string>
    <string name="reset_frame_position_size">إعادة تعيين موضع الإطار وحجمه</string>
    <string name="on_lock_screen">على شاشة القفل</string>
    <string name="in_notification_center">في مركز الاشعارات</string>
    <string name="in_locked_notification_center">في مركز الإشعارات المقفل</string>
    <string name="reset_frame_position_size_confirm_message">هل أنت متأكد من أنك تريد إعادة تعيين الموقع والحجم؟</string>
    <string name="install_shizuku">تثبيت تطبيقات</string>
    <string name="open_shizuku">فتح تطبيقات</string>
    <string name="grant_read_media_images">منح قراءة الوسائط والصور</string>
    <string name="failed_to_add_shortcut">غير قادر على إضافة الاختصار.</string>
    <string name="directly_check_for_activity">التحقق مباشرة من النشاط</string>
    <string name="directly_check_for_activity_desc">عند التمكين، ستستخدم تطبيقات مصغرة قفل الشاشة API لنظام أندرويد للتحقق مما إذا كان يتم تشغيل نشاط النقر على عنصر واجهة المستخدم. يمكن أن يكون هذا أسرع من الكشف المدمج لشاشة القفل، ولكن قد يسبب إيجابيات زائفة.</string>
    <string name="translate">ترجمة</string>
    <string name="translate_desc">ساعد بترجمة تطبيقات مصغرة الى لغتك.</string>
    <string name="error_reconfiguring_widget">Error reconfiguring widget</string>
</resources>
